0,0,DESC,How did serfdom develop in and then leave Russia ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'CCONJ', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
1,1,ENTY,What films featured the character Popeye Doyle ?,cremat,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
2,2,DESC,How can I find a list of celebrities ' real names ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
3,3,ENTY,What fowl grabs the spotlight after the Chinese Year of the Monkey ?,animal,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', '']"
4,4,ABBR,What is the full form of .com ?,exp,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'X', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
5,5,HUM,What contemptible scoundrel stole the cork from my lunch ?,ind,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
6,6,HUM,What team did baseball 's St. Louis Browns become ?,gr,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', 'GPE', '', '', '']"
7,7,HUM,What is the oldest profession ?,title,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
8,8,DESC,What are liver enzymes ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
9,9,HUM,Name the scar-faced bounty hunter of The Old West .,ind,"['VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
11,11,DESC,Why do heavier objects travel downhill faster ?,reason,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'ADV', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
13,13,HUM,Who killed Gandhi ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', '']"
14,14,ENTY,What is considered the costliest disaster the insurance industry has ever faced ?,event,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
15,15,LOC,What sprawling U.S. state boasts the most airports ?,state,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'GPE', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
16,16,DESC,What did the only repealed amendment to the U.S. Constitution deal with ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'LAW', 'LAW', 'LAW', '', '', '']"
17,17,NUM,How many Jews were executed in concentration camps during WWII ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'EVENT', '']"
18,18,DESC,What is `` Nine Inch Nails '' ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
19,19,DESC,What is an annotated bibliography ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
20,20,NUM,What is the date of Boxing Day ?,date,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'DATE', 'DATE', '']"
21,21,ENTY,What articles of clothing are tokens in Monopoly ?,other,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
22,22,HUM,Name 11 famous martyrs .,ind,"['NOUN', 'NUM', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'CARDINAL', '', '', '']"
23,23,DESC,What 's the Olympic motto ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
24,24,DESC,What is the origin of the name ` Scarlett ' ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '']"
25,25,ENTY,What 's the second-most-used vowel in English ?,letter,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'LANGUAGE', '']"
26,26,HUM,Who was the inventor of silly putty ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
28,28,ENTY,Name a golf course in Myrtle Beach .,other,"['VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', 'GPE', '']"
29,29,LOC,Which two states enclose Chesapeake Bay ?,state,"['DET', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'CARDINAL', '', '', 'LOC', 'LOC', '']"
30,30,ABBR,What does the abbreviation AIDS stand for ?,exp,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
31,31,ENTY,What does a spermologer collect ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
32,32,NUM,How many points make up a perfect fivepin bowling score ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PART', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
33,33,HUM,Which company that manufactures video-game hardware sells the `` super system '' ?,gr,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PUNCT', 'PART', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
34,34,NUM,How many Community Chest cards are there in Monopoly ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
35,35,DESC,What do Mormons believe ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
36,36,NUM,When did the neanderthal man live ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
37,37,ENTY,In what religion was Isis the nature goddess ?,religion,"['ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '']"
38,38,LOC,Where do the adventures of `` The Swiss Family Robinson '' take place ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
39,39,ENTY,What relative of the racoon is sometimes known as the cat-bear ?,animal,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
40,40,DESC,How can I register my website in Yahoo for free ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', '', '']"
41,41,ENTY,What was cash-conscious Colonel Edwin L. Drake the first to drill ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PART', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '', '']"
42,42,NUM,How many people in the world speak French ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'LANGUAGE', '']"
43,43,NUM,How many inches over six feet is the Venus de Milo ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'FAC', 'FAC', 'FAC', 'FAC', '']"
44,44,DESC,How do they find or choose witnesses to an execution ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
45,45,HUM,What 1920s cowboy star rode Tony the Wonder Horse ?,ind,"['PRON', 'NUM', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'DATE', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '']"
46,46,ENTY,What cocktail inspired John Doxat to write the book Stirred-Not Shaken ?,food,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', 'FAC', 'FAC', 'FAC', 'FAC', '']"
47,47,HUM,What ISPs exist in the Caribbean ?,gr,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', '']"
48,48,DESC,How do you ask a total stranger out on a date ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
49,49,ENTY,What weapon is the mythological character Apollo most proficient with ?,other,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '', '', '', '']"
50,50,LOC,What country do the Galapagos Islands belong to ?,country,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'LOC', 'LOC', '', '', '']"
51,51,DESC,What is ethology ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '']"
52,52,HUM,Who was the prophet of the Muslim people ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'NORP', '', '']"
53,53,DESC,Where did the term `` 86ed '' come from ?,desc,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '', '', '']"
54,54,HUM,Who is Snoopy 's arch-enemy ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '']"
55,55,DESC,What is the nature of learning ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
56,56,ENTY,What 's the only color Johnny Cash wears on stage ?,color,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '']"
57,57,ENTY,What 's the term for a young fox ?,termeq,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
58,58,LOC,What U.S. state lived under six flags ?,state,"['PRON', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'GPE', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '']"
59,59,DESC,What is the Kashmir issue ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'LOC', '', '']"
60,60,LOC,Where is the Loop ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORG', '']"
61,61,DESC,What does `` extended definition '' mean and how would one write a paper on it ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NUM', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
62,62,LOC,What country 's capital is Tirana ?,country,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
63,63,DESC,What is titanium ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '']"
64,64,HUM,Who do Herb and Tootsie live next door to ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'NORP', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '']"
65,65,LOC,Which city has the oldest relationship as a sisterðcity with Los Angeles ?,city,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', 'GPE', '']"
66,66,DESC,What is a caldera ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
67,67,DESC,Why do people get calluses ?,reason,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
68,68,LOC,What are the names of the tourist attractions in Reims ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
69,69,DESC,What are Cushman and Wakefield known for ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'NORP', '', 'GPE', '', '', '']"
70,70,LOC,What body of water does the Danube River flow into ?,other,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', 'LOC', '', '', '']"
71,71,HUM,Who is the founder of Scientology ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
72,72,ENTY,What does the six-footed Musca domestica become when it enters a house ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
73,73,DESC,What is the history of skateboarding ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
74,74,HUM,Who starred in Singing in the Rain and The Singing Nun ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', '']"
75,75,DESC,How do I make fuel bricks from recycled newspaper ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
76,76,HUM,What 19th-century painter died in the Marquesas Islands ?,ind,"['DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', '', '', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', '']"
77,77,ENTY,The corpus callosum is in what part of the body ?,body,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
78,78,DESC,How do I log on to home page at Headquarters U.S. European Command ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PART', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
79,79,LOC,"What country did the Nazis occupy for 1 , CD NNS IN NNP NNP NNP .",country,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'NORP', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '', 'ORG', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
80,80,ENTY,What is Nebraska 's most valuable resource ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '']"
81,81,NUM,How many species of the Great White shark are there ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '', '', '']"
82,82,DESC,What is the origin of head lice ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
83,83,LOC,What is the nickname for the state of Mississippi ?,state,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
84,84,ENTY,What was the first domesticated bird ?,animal,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '', '']"
85,85,NUM,How many villi are found in the small intestine ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
86,86,LOC,What country did King Wenceslas rule ?,country,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '']"
87,87,ENTY,What is a fear of shadows ?,dismed,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
88,88,HUM,Who were the five Marx brothers ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', '', '']"
89,89,NUM,In which year was New Zealand excluded from the ANZUS alliance ?,date,"['ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', 'GPE', 'GPE', '', '', '', 'ORG', '', '']"
90,90,NUM,When did CNN begin broadcasting ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', '', '', '']"
91,91,DESC,What causes the body to shiver in cold temperatures ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
92,92,DESC,What are bear and bull markets ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
93,93,ENTY,What J.R.R. Tolkien book features Bilbo Baggins as the central character ?,cremat,"['PRON', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '']"
94,94,DESC,What is `` dew point '' ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
95,95,DESC,What is the meaning of Jesus ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '']"
96,96,HUM,What company 's logo is a `` W '' in a circle ?,gr,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
97,97,DESC,What is the definition of a cascade ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
98,98,NUM,When did Rococo painting and architecture flourish ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '']"
99,99,LOC,What country 's national passenger rail system is called Via ?,country,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
100,100,HUM,Who invented Make-up ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
101,101,DESC,What is the origin of the word `` attic '' ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
102,102,DESC,What did Delilah do to Samson 's hair ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', '', '', 'ORG', '', '', '']"
103,103,ENTY,What kind of animals were in the Paleozoic era ?,animal,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', '']"
104,104,HUM,Which of the following was Rhodes Scholar ?,ind,"['DET', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
105,105,HUM,Who comprised the now-defunct comic book team known as the Champions ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '']"
106,106,DESC,How do you make a paintball ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
107,107,LOC,What U.S. state is Fort Knox in ?,state,"['PRON', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADV', 'PUNCT']","['', 'GPE', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '']"
108,108,ENTY,What is a female rabbit called ?,animal,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
109,109,LOC,Where is the highest point in Japan ?,mount,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
110,110,DESC,Where do chihuahuas come from ?,desc,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
111,111,LOC,Where does Barney Rubble go to work after he drops Fred off in the `` Flintstones '' cartoon series ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '', 'PRODUCT', '', '', '', '']"
112,112,LOC,What are the world 's four oceans ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '']"
113,113,ENTY,What 's the only work by Michelangelo that bears his signature ?,cremat,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'DET', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '']"
114,114,ENTY,What is the largest snake in the world ?,animal,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
115,115,ENTY,In what medium is Stuart Hamblen considered to be the first singing cowboy ?,cremat,"['ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PART', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '', '']"
116,116,LOC,Where on the Internet can I find a song lyrics database similar to the International Lyrics Server ?,other,"['ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
117,117,NUM,How much money does a back injury lawsuit get ?,money,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
118,118,ENTY,What 's the common name for acetylsalicylic acid ?,termeq,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
119,119,DESC,What does the Georgetown `` Hoya '' mean ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORG', '', '', 'ORG', '', '', '']"
120,120,LOC,Where can I find a list of `` classic '' books 5th and 6th graders should read ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORDINAL', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '', '', '']"
121,121,ENTY,Which two products use a tiger as their symbol ?,product,"['DET', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'CARDINAL', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
122,122,DESC,How is the election of a new Pope announced to the world ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '']"
123,123,NUM,How long does it take for your blood to make one complete trip through the body ?,period,"['ADV', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NUM', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
124,124,DESC,How do chickens have baby chicks ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
125,125,DESC,What is the historical relationship of Catholic Church and bingo ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '', '']"
126,126,DESC,How was the element calcium named ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
127,127,HUM,What crooner joined The Andrews Sisters for Pistol Packin Mama ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', '', '', '', '', '']"
128,128,HUM,What piano company claims its product is the `` Instrument of the immortals '' ?,gr,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
129,129,NUM,When did the Bounty mutiny take place ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '']"
130,130,ENTY,What novel inspired the movie BladeRunner ?,cremat,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '']"
131,131,DESC,What is a transistor ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
132,132,ENTY,What is a film starring Jude Law ?,cremat,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
133,133,ENTY,What Hollywood dog died in the arms of Jean Harlow in 1932 ?,animal,"['PRON', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', 'GPE', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', 'DATE', '']"
134,134,ENTY,What are the most common elements in the Earth 's crust ?,substance,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', '', '', '']"
135,135,NUM,"How much would it cost to purchase a 2-foot-square party tent , with sides , ?",money,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PART', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
136,136,HUM,What actress has received the most Oscar nominations ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADV', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'FAC', '', '']"
137,137,DESC,What are equity securities ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
138,138,DESC,What is gymnophobia ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '']"
139,139,NUM,How many years do fossils take to form ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PART', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
140,140,LOC,Where is the Orinoco ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORG', '']"
141,141,ENTY,What was the name of the `` Little Rascals '' dog ?,animal,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
142,142,LOC,"What city boasts Penn 's Landing , on the banks of the Delaware river ?",city,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', '']"
143,143,ENTY,What Broadway musical was inspired by Cervantes 's Don Quixote ?,cremat,"['PRON', 'PROPN', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'FAC', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
144,144,DESC,"What is the origin of the word , JJ .",desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PRODUCT', '']"
145,145,NUM,How many hostages were killed in the Entebbe raid ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '']"
146,146,DESC,How you can raise your IQ ?,manner,"['ADV', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
147,147,ABBR,What does INRI stand for when used on Jesus ' cross ?,exp,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
148,148,HUM,Who produces Spumante ?,gr,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', '']"
149,149,HUM,Who earns their money the hard way ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
150,150,HUM,Who founded the People 's Temple Commune ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
151,151,HUM,What athlete makes the most money from sports merchandise sales ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
152,152,NUM,How many bends are there in a standard paper clip ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
153,153,HUM,Who discovered electricity ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '']"
154,154,ENTY,What part of your body contains the corpus callosum ?,body,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
155,155,HUM,Who was the first American in space ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORDINAL', 'NORP', '', '', '']"
156,156,LOC,What two South American countries do n't border Brazil ?,country,"['PRON', 'NUM', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'CARDINAL', 'NORP', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
158,158,ENTY,"What poem contains the line , `` grow old with me the best is yet to be '' .",cremat,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'PART', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
159,159,DESC,What is a dental root canal ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
160,160,ENTY,What war did the Wanna-Go-Home Riots occur after ?,event,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
161,161,NUM,What is the busiest air travel season ?,date,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'DATE', '']"
162,162,ENTY,What 's the colored part of the eye called ?,body,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
163,163,DESC,What are hook worms ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
164,164,LOC,Where is the Rose Bowl played ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', '', '']"
165,165,HUM,Which Japanese car maker had its biggest percentage of sale in the domestic market ?,gr,"['DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
166,166,HUM,Who is the mayor of Marbella ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
167,167,LOC,"What sun-blasted , 14-mile wide valley is just north of the Mojave desert ?",other,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '']"
168,168,NUM,In what year did Thatcher become prime minister ?,date,"['ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '']"
169,169,NUM,How many months does it take the moon to revolve around the Earth ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', '']"
170,170,LOC,Where are the 49 steps ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '']"
171,171,NUM,In what year was De Gaulle elected president of France ?,date,"['ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
172,172,HUM,Who sings the themes for `` Dawson 's Creek '' and `` Felicity '' ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', '', '']"
173,173,HUM,Who directed `` Jaws '' ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', '', '']"
174,174,ENTY,On what T.V. show could Tom Terrific be found ?,cremat,"['ADP', 'PRON', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
175,175,HUM,What Indian tribe is F Troop perpetually doing battle with ?,gr,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '']"
176,176,DESC,Where did Indian Pudding come from ?,desc,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'NORP', '', '', '', '']"
177,177,DESC,Why do some clothing labels say `` Use a nonchlorine bleach '' ?,reason,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
178,178,NUM,How many colonies were involved in the American Revolution ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', '']"
179,179,LOC,What is the name of the city that Maurizio Pellegrin lives in ?,city,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
180,180,LOC,Where can I find pictorial directions on how to build a very simple treehouse ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'PART', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
181,181,ENTY,"What game 's board shows the territories of Irkutsk , Yakutsk and Kamchatka ?",sport,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', 'GPE', '', 'GPE', '']"
182,182,HUM,What is the name of the managing director of Apricot Computer ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
183,183,HUM,What is the occupation of Nicholas Cage ?,title,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
184,184,DESC,Why do horseshoes bring luck ?,reason,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
185,185,DESC,"What is the 401 , K , plan ?",def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', 'ORG', '', '', '']"
186,186,DESC,What causes pneumonia ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '']"
187,187,NUM,What are the three winter months in the southern hemisphere ?,date,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', '', '', '', '']"
188,188,DESC,What does gringo mean ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
189,189,LOC,What country contains Africa 's northernmost point ?,country,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'LOC', '', '', '', '']"
190,190,ENTY,What therapy attempts to elicit the `` primal scream '' ?,dismed,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PART', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
191,191,LOC,Where is the Kalahari desert ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '']"
192,192,HUM,Which Ventura County police department seized the largest cocaine shipment in it 's history ?,gr,"['DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'GPE', 'GPE', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
193,193,LOC,What city is sometimes called Gotham ?,city,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '']"
194,194,ENTY,What dangles over the tongue from the palate ?,body,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
195,195,HUM,Who created Dennis the Menace ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
196,196,HUM,What dummy received an honorary degree from Northwestern University ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
197,197,NUM,When was the first Wall Street Journal published ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORDINAL', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '']"
198,198,LOC,What countries have the largest areas of forest ?,country,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
199,199,DESC,How do I start a web based business ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
200,200,HUM,Name Alvin 's brothers,ind,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
201,201,DESC,What is Eagle 's syndrome styloid process ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '']"
202,202,DESC,How did Jayne Mansfield die ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '']"
203,203,NUM,When did the royal wedding of Prince Andrew and Fergie take place ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
204,204,HUM,What actor said in A Day at the Races : `` Either he 's dead or my watch has stopped '' ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
205,205,HUM,What explorer was nicknamed Iberia 's Pilot ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', '', '']"
206,206,NUM,CNN began broadcasting in what year ?,date,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['ORG', '', '', '', 'DATE', 'DATE', '']"
207,207,ENTY,What is a ball that hits the foul pole called ?,termeq,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'DET', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
208,208,DESC,What makes hamburgers taste like steakburgers ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
209,209,HUM,Which company created the Internet browser Mosaic ?,gr,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '']"
210,210,ENTY,What are the rites accompanying the circumcision of a newly born-child in Judaism called ?,event,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '', '']"
211,211,ENTY,What was the education system in the 1960 's ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PART', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'DATE', '', '']"
212,212,LOC,What South American city has the world 's highest commercial landing field ?,city,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
213,213,DESC,How can I find out which cities have cable-modem access ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PART', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
214,214,DESC,What is Betsy Ross famous for ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
215,215,NUM,How many species of sharks are there ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
216,216,DESC,What is `` snoogans '' ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
217,217,NUM,How many people are there in the world ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
218,218,ENTY,What shrubs can be planted that will be safe from deer ?,plant,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'DET', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
219,219,HUM,What organization 's offices were broken into at Watergate in 1972 ?,gr,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'EVENT', '', 'DATE', '']"
220,220,DESC,What is the design of the ship Titanic ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
221,221,ABBR,What does S.O.S. stand for ?,exp,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', '', '', '']"
222,222,ENTY,Name a technique widely used to detect birth defects ?,techmeth,"['VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
223,223,DESC,What is the daily requirement of folic acid for an expectant mother ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'DATE', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
224,224,DESC,What is the `` 7-minute cigarette '' ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
225,225,ENTY,What four forms does gold occur in ?,other,"['PRON', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', 'CARDINAL', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
226,226,NUM,What is the acreage of the Chappellet vineyard ?,volsize,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '', '']"
227,227,DESC,How do you correctly say the word ` qigong ' ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
228,228,NUM,When did beethoven die ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
229,229,NUM,How much does a new railroad coal car cost ?,money,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
230,230,LOC,What two European countries entered the War of American Independence against the British ?,country,"['PRON', 'NUM', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'CARDINAL', 'NORP', '', '', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', '', '', 'NORP', '']"
231,231,DESC,What is the filmmakers collabrative ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
232,232,HUM,What Russian composer 's Prelude in C Sharp Minor brought him fame and fortune ?,ind,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
233,233,DESC,What caused Harry Houdini 's death ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '']"
234,234,HUM,"Who was the mother of the man who would not be king , the duke of Windsor ?",ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
235,235,NUM,How many revolutions does a standard LP make in three minutes ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '', '', 'TIME', 'TIME', '']"
237,237,LOC,Where can I find a review of Nightmare on Elm Street in a film journal ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '']"
238,238,ENTY,What 's the slowest Olympic swimming stroke ?,techmeth,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'LOC', '', '', '']"
239,239,HUM,What was the name of the first Russian astronaut to do a spacewalk ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORDINAL', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
240,240,ENTY,What disease is transmitted by the Anopheles mosquito ?,dismed,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'NORP', '', '']"
241,241,ENTY,What rum is so `` mixable '' it is a one-brand bar ?,food,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '', '', '']"
242,242,NUM,How many South American countries have the letter Z in their names ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'NORP', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
243,243,DESC,What is the contents of proposition 98 ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '']"
245,245,NUM,"How many people on the ground were killed from the bombing of Pan Am Flight 103 over Lockerbie , Scotland , December 21 , CD .",count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NUM', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PRODUCT', 'PRODUCT', 'PRODUCT', 'PRODUCT', '', 'GPE', '', 'GPE', '', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', '', '']"
246,246,HUM,Who wrote NN DT NNP NNP '' ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '']"
247,247,DESC,What is paracetamol ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '']"
248,248,DESC,What are the powers and weaknesses of Green Lantern 's ring ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '']"
250,250,NUM,When was the first steel mill in the United States built ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', '', '']"
251,251,HUM,What diminutive American female gymnast stole the show at the 1984 Olympics ?,ind,"['DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', '']"
252,252,DESC,What is the origin of the name Katie ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '']"
254,254,NUM,When did the Berlin Wall go up ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PART', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'FAC', 'FAC', 'FAC', '', '', '']"
255,255,HUM,Who is Terrence Malick ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
256,256,ENTY,What instrument is Ray Charles best known for playing ?,instru,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '']"
257,257,DESC,"What 's the meaning of the Latin battle cry : Ad arma , ad arma .",def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
259,259,LOC,"What Las Vegas hotel burned in November , 1980 , with the loss of 84 lives ?",other,"['PRON', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'GPE', 'GPE', '', '', '', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', '', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '']"
260,260,NUM,When did Mount St. Helen last have a significant eruption ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
261,261,ABBR,CNN is the abbreviation for what ?,exp,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'PUNCT']","['ORG', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
262,262,NUM,When did World War I start ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', '', '']"
263,263,NUM,How many feet are there in a fathom ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
264,264,DESC,What is a Canada two-penny black ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'GPE', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', '', '']"
265,265,LOC,What European city do Nicois live in ?,city,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
266,266,DESC,How can I find out what year a Beanie Baby was introduced ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PART', 'PRON', 'NOUN', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
267,267,DESC,What is the classic definition of tragic hero ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
268,268,ENTY,To what does Microsoft 's Windows 3 owe its success ?,other,"['ADP', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'PROPN', 'NUM', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORG', '', 'PRODUCT', 'PRODUCT', '', '', '', '']"
269,269,HUM,Who was President of Afghanistan in 1994 ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', 'DATE', '']"
270,270,ENTY,"What are other ways of getting stretch marks besides pregnancy , weight loss , and weight lifting ?",techmeth,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
271,271,ENTY,What did brontosauruses eat ?,food,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
272,272,ENTY,What color bottles do good Rhine wines come in ?,color,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PART', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '', '', '', '']"
273,273,HUM,Who was the lead actress in the movie ` Sleepless in Seattle ' ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'FAC', '', 'GPE', '', '']"
275,275,HUM,Who are the two sons of Ozzie and Harriet Nelson ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
276,276,DESC,What is molybdenum ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '']"
277,277,NUM,When is Boxing Day ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'DATE', 'DATE', '']"
278,278,ENTY,What is the lowest level of the American judiciary ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'NORP', '', '']"
279,279,NUM,When was the battle of the Somme fought ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '', '']"
280,280,NUM,How many people did Randy Craft kill ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '']"
282,282,NUM,When did Spielberg direct `` Jaws '' ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '']"
283,283,NUM,What is the size of the largest akita ?,volsize,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
284,284,ENTY,What animal has the biggest eyes ?,animal,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
285,285,LOC,What is California 's capital ?,city,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'GPE', '', '', '']"
287,287,HUM,Who was the founding member of the Pink Floyd band ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '']"
288,288,LOC,What European country is home to the beer-producing city of Budweis ?,country,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
289,289,DESC,How do I find the balance of my social security account ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
290,290,DESC,What is the history of Valentine 's Day cards ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', 'PERSON', '', '']"
292,292,ENTY,What do Italians call Florence ?,termeq,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'NORP', '', 'PERSON', '']"
294,294,ABBR,What does ` PSI ' stand for ?,exp,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORG', '', '', '', '']"
295,295,LOC,What sea did the Romans call mare nostrum ?,other,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'NORP', '', '', '', '']"
296,296,ENTY,What 's the term for a bet before cards are dealt ?,termeq,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
297,297,ENTY,"Which came first , according to Genesis 1 : 2 : 22 - the chicken or the egg ?",animal,"['DET', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NUM', 'SYM', 'NUM', 'SYM', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', 'CARDINAL', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
298,298,LOC,What city did the Flintstones live in ?,city,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
299,299,ENTY,What is Latin for incompetent ?,termeq,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'NORP', '', '', '']"
300,300,ENTY,What chemicals are used in lethal injection ?,dismed,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
301,301,HUM,What toy company is the world 's No.1 maker of female apparel ?,gr,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PRODUCT', '', '', '', '', '']"
302,302,ENTY,What board game does a `` wood-pusher '' play poorly ?,sport,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
303,303,HUM,Which Doonesbury character was likely to turn into a werewolf ?,ind,"['DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PART', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
304,304,ABBR,What is the abbreviation for micro ?,abb,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
305,305,ENTY,What are the 7 articles of the constitution ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '', '', '', '']"
306,306,HUM,Who has won the most Super Bowls ?,gr,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADV', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'FAC', 'FAC', '']"
307,307,ABBR,What does NASDAQ stand for ?,exp,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', '', '', '']"
308,308,ABBR,What is BPH ?,exp,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '']"
309,309,ENTY,What is the fastest commercial automobile that can be bought in the US ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'DET', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
310,310,LOC,What stadium do the Miami Dolphins play their home games in ?,other,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
311,311,HUM,Who has the only speaking role in `` Silent Movie '' ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
312,312,DESC,Why is poop sometimes different colors ?,reason,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
313,313,NUM,What was Einstein 's IQ ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
314,314,NUM,What day was Pearl Harbor attacked in 1942 ?,date,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', 'DATE', '']"
315,315,HUM,What girl 's name is `` Teddy '' an affectionate form of ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
316,316,LOC,What state is John F. Kennedy buried in ?,state,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PART', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
318,318,LOC,What U.S. state has an element named for it ?,state,"['PRON', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'PUNCT']","['', 'GPE', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
319,319,HUM,What company tabulates the ballots in voting for the Academy Awards ?,gr,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
320,320,DESC,How did the tradition of best man start ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
321,321,NUM,How many years ago did the ship Titanic sink ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', '', '', 'ORG', '', '']"
322,322,LOC,What is the deepest area of the Arctic Ocean ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', '']"
323,323,ENTY,What are Halloween 's colors ?,color,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'DATE', '', '', '']"
324,324,DESC,How is silk screening done ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
325,325,NUM,"What is the latitude and longitude of El Paso , Texas ?",other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', 'GPE', '', 'GPE', '']"
326,326,HUM,Who made a boat out of gopher wood ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
327,327,LOC,Where can I find a `` Fifth Element '' screensaver ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
328,328,HUM,Which Bloom County resident wreaks havoc with a computer ?,ind,"['DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'GPE', 'GPE', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
329,329,DESC,How do you match a name to a social security number ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
330,330,DESC,How does a rainbow form ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
331,331,NUM,What is the normal resting heart rate of a healthy adult ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
332,332,NUM,What is the population of Ohio ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
333,333,NUM,How many calories are there in a Big Mac ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
334,334,DESC,Hazmat stands for what ?,def,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
335,335,ENTY,What creature scares people in the film `` Jaws '' ?,animal,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', '', '']"
336,336,HUM,What part did John Peter Zenger play in the deveopment of the newspaper in America ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
337,337,HUM,Who followed Caesar ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', '']"
338,338,ENTY,What are the four elements ?,substance,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '']"
339,339,HUM,Who was the first woman golfer to earn a million ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL', '']"
340,340,ENTY,What 's the tallest piece on a chessboard ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
341,341,LOC,What is Answers.com 's address ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', '', '', '']"
342,342,LOC,Where can I buy movies on videotape online ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
343,343,HUM,Who does the advertizing for Frito-Lay ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
344,344,HUM,Who is the leading competitor of Trans Union Company ?,gr,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
345,345,ENTY,What product did Robert Conrad dare people to knock off his shoulder ?,product,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'PART', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
346,346,HUM,Who invented the radio ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
347,347,NUM,What 's the American dollar equivalent for 8 pounds in the U.K. ?,count,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'NORP', '', '', '', 'QUANTITY', 'QUANTITY', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
348,348,ENTY,What are the different approaches of systems analysis ?,techmeth,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
349,349,DESC,How do doctors diagnose bone cancer ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
350,350,HUM,Who is the man behind the pig-the man who pulls the strings and speaks for Miss Piggy ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '']"
351,351,NUM,What is the speed of the Mississippi River ?,speed,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', '']"
352,352,ENTY,What are the developmental stages of a swimmer ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
353,353,HUM,What actor first portrayed James Bond ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
354,354,LOC,What ocean is the largest in the world ?,other,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
355,355,HUM,"Who was the first American poet to win the Nobel Prize for literature , in 1948 ?",ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORDINAL', 'NORP', '', '', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', '', '', '', '', 'DATE', '']"
356,356,NUM,What year did Jack Nicklaus join the Professional Golfers Association tour ?,date,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['DATE', 'DATE', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '']"
357,357,NUM,How many sonnets did Shakespeare write ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '']"
358,358,DESC,What causes the redness in your cheeks when you blush ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
359,359,HUM,Who won the Nobel Peace Prize in 1991 ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', '', 'DATE', '']"
360,360,HUM,Who are the Challengers of the Unknown ?,gr,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
361,361,DESC,Define the Pheonix Club ?,def,"['VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
362,362,LOC,Which city did Christian Crusaders fight to recapture from the Muslims ?,city,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PART', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '', 'NORP', '']"
363,363,DESC,What does it mean `` Rupee Depreciates '' ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
364,364,ENTY,What gaming devices were dubbed `` Mississippi marbles '' and `` Memphis dominoes '' ?,other,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', '', '', '']"
365,365,HUM,Who was the first coach of the Cleveland Browns ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
366,366,DESC,How successful is arometherapy ?,manner,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
367,367,ENTY,What Jewish holiday saw the start of the 1973 Mideast War ?,event,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'DATE', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', '']"
368,368,DESC,How does a copier work ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
369,369,NUM,What is the speed of the Mississippi River ?,speed,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', '']"
370,370,HUM,Who said of Super Bowl III in 1969 : `` We 'll win- I guarantee it '' ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', '', 'DATE', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
371,371,ENTY,What is Dudley Do-Right 's horse 's name ?,animal,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '']"
372,372,HUM,Who declared : `` I am down on whores and I shan 't stop ripping them '' ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
373,373,LOC,Where does chocolate come from ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
374,374,ENTY,What TV game show once saw a contestant admit to picking his toes in the shower ?,cremat,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
375,375,HUM,What Soviet leader owned a Rolls-Royce ?,ind,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
376,376,LOC,Where can I find a case on Individuals with Disabilities Education Act of 1991 ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', 'DATE', '']"
377,377,ENTY,What war did Florence Nightingale tend the troops in ?,event,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '']"
378,378,HUM,"Who wrote the song , `` Stardust '' ?",ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', '', '']"
379,379,NUM,How many Beatles ' records went #1 ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SYM', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', 'MONEY', '']"
380,380,HUM,Who is the only prime minister of Canada to serve 22 years but not necessarily consecutively ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADV', 'ADV', 'ADV', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', '', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', '', '', '', '']"
381,381,ABBR,What is the abbreviation of the company name ` General Motors ' ?,abb,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
382,382,LOC,What mountains lie between the Arkansas and Missouri rivers ?,mount,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', 'GPE', '', '']"
383,383,HUM,Who received the Will Rogers Award in 1989 ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', '', 'DATE', '']"
384,384,DESC,What is the function of RAM ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '']"
385,385,LOC,What 's the closest G2 Spectrum Yellow Dwarf to Earth ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'NORP', 'LOC', 'LOC', '', '', 'LOC', '']"
386,386,NUM,How many equal angles are there in an isosceles triangle ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
387,387,ENTY,What is the fear of cockroaches called ?,dismed,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
388,388,ENTY,What CBS soap opera was interrupted by the bulletin of John F. Kennedy 's assassination ?,cremat,"['PRON', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '']"
389,389,DESC,What is the use of a 24-hour clock instead of a 12-hour clock ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
390,390,HUM,What was the name of the lawyer who represented Randy Craft ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
391,391,HUM,What United States President had dreamed that he was assassinated ?,ind,"['PRON', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', 'GPE', 'GPE', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
392,392,ENTY,What film did Lee Marvin win the 1965 best actor Oscar for ?,cremat,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', 'DATE', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '']"
393,393,LOC,Where is Basque country located ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'NORP', '', '', '']"
394,394,ENTY,What product does `` Mrs. Olsen '' promote ?,product,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
395,395,NUM,What time of day did Emperor Hirohito die ?,date,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '']"
396,396,DESC,What is dry ice ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
397,397,ENTY,What 's the most powerful card in Euchre ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
398,398,DESC,What does `` intractable plantar keratoma '' mean ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
399,399,NUM,How many years did it take James Joyce to write Ulysses ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', 'ORG', '']"
400,400,ENTY,What crop failure caused the Irish Famine ?,food,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'NORP', '', '']"
401,401,LOC,What South Korean city is served by Kimpo International Airport ?,city,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
402,402,NUM,How many types of dogs ' tails are there - three,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'NUM']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL']"
403,403,ENTY,What is the longest-running television series ?,cremat,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
404,404,ENTY,What predators exist on Antarctica ?,animal,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'LOC', '']"
405,405,DESC,What is the difference between a generator and an alternator ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
406,406,DESC,How is energy created ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
407,407,ENTY,What beer advertised that it had `` three rings '' ?,food,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '', '']"
408,408,NUM,What is the quantity of American soldiers still unaccounted for from the Vietnam war ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', '']"
409,409,ENTY,What golfing accessory was patented by George Grant on December 12,techmeth,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NUM']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', 'DATE', 'DATE']"
410,410,ENTY,What are the different types of plastic ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
411,411,DESC,How is it correct to say ` qigong ' ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'ADJ', 'PART', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
412,412,LOC,What was the highest mountain on earth before Mount Everest was discovered ?,mount,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', 'LOC', '', '', '']"
413,413,LOC,"Where was the Ligurian Republic , 1797-185 , ?",other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'SYM', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
414,414,LOC,What country 's people are the top television watchers ?,country,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
415,415,NUM,When was the women 's suffrage amendment ratified ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
416,416,HUM,What Polynesian people inhabit New Zealand ?,gr,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', '', '', 'GPE', 'GPE', '']"
417,417,ENTY,What movie tour of the Roman empire features the admonition : `` Row well and live '' ?,cremat,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
418,418,LOC,What Nevada center has been dubbed The Biggest Little City in the World ?,city,"['PRON', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'GPE', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '', 'ORG', '']"
419,419,HUM,"What President lived at 219 North Delaware Street , Independence , Missouri ?",ind,"['PRON', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', '', 'GPE', '', 'GPE', '']"
420,420,DESC,Give a reason for American Indians oftentimes dropping out of school .,reason,"['VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
421,421,LOC,Where must a soccer goalie stand to be permitted to handle the ball ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PART', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PART', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
422,422,DESC,What is the difference between classical conditioning and operant conditioning ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
423,423,LOC,In what U.S. state was the first woman governor elected ?,state,"['ADP', 'PRON', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'GPE', '', '', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '', '', '']"
424,424,DESC,What are some interesting facts and information about dogsledding ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
425,425,NUM,What year did Hitler die ?,date,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['DATE', 'DATE', '', 'PERSON', '', '']"
426,426,HUM,What famous model was married to Billy Joel ?,ind,"['DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
427,427,ENTY,What kind of animal is Babar ?,animal,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', '']"
428,428,DESC,What is Jane Goodall known for ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
429,429,ENTY,What killed Bob Marley ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
430,430,NUM,How much money are Dumbo 's ears insured for ?,money,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '']"
431,431,HUM,Who danced into stardom with Fred Astaire in 1941 's You 'll Never Get Rich ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PART', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', 'DATE', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
432,432,HUM,Who is Stein Eriksen ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
433,433,DESC,What does the name Billie mean ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PRODUCT', '', '']"
435,435,LOC,What is the highest peak in Africa ?,mount,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', '']"
436,436,LOC,Where is Procter & Gamble headquartered in the U.S. ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
437,437,LOC,What desert has been called The Garden of Allah ?,other,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', '']"
438,438,ENTY,What do bicornate animals have two of ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NUM', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '']"
439,439,DESC,What function does a community 's water tower serve ?,reason,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
440,440,ENTY,What is a fear of weakness ?,dismed,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
441,441,NUM,How many miles is it to Ohio from North Carolina ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', 'GPE', 'GPE', '']"
442,442,NUM,How much snow equals an inch of rain ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
443,443,ABBR,What does G.M.T. stand for ?,exp,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
444,444,DESC,What does Inuit and Eskimo mean ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', '', 'PERSON', '', '']"
445,445,ENTY,What song served as the closing theme of The Johnny Cash Show ?,cremat,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', '']"
446,446,ENTY,What field sport did dentist William Beers promote and write a standard book of rules for ?,sport,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
447,447,DESC,How do I tie dye clothes ?,manner,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
448,448,NUM,When does the average teenager first have intercourse ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
449,449,DESC,Why doesn 't www.answers.com have any answers to my questions ?,reason,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
450,450,HUM,What actor 's autobiography is titled All My Yesterdays ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'DET', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
451,451,HUM,What Russian master spy lived in the U.S. under the name Emil Goldfus ?,ind,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
452,452,LOC,Where 's the 19th hole on a golf course ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
453,453,DESC,What 's nature 's purpose for tornadoes ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
454,454,HUM,Who played the original Charlie 's Angels ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', '']"
455,455,LOC,Where can I find a person 's address from a telephone number ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
456,456,ENTY,"What English word comes from the Old French covrefeu , meaning cover fire ?",word,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', 'NORP', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
457,457,ENTY,What musical instrument did Prewitt play in James Jones 's From Here to Eternity ?,instru,"['DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', 'ORG', '']"
458,458,LOC,Where did Sarge Steel get his metal hand ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '', '', '', '', '']"
459,459,DESC,What makes popcorn pop ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
461,461,ENTY,Where does your hair grow the fastest ?,body,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
462,462,LOC,What country did King Gustav V reign over from 197 to 195 ?,country,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', 'CARDINAL', '']"
463,463,HUM,Who painted Mother and Child ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', 'PERSON', '']"
464,464,NUM,What is the speed of the Mississippi River ?,speed,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', '']"
465,465,LOC,In what area of the world was the Six Day War fought ?,other,"['ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', '', '']"
466,466,LOC,What is the brightest star visible from Earth ?,other,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'LOC', '']"
467,467,ENTY,What film marked Robert Redford 's directorial debut ?,cremat,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
468,468,HUM,What was Mao 's second name ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'PERSON', '', 'ORDINAL', '', '']"
469,469,ENTY,What film or films has Jude Law appeared in ?,cremat,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PART', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '']"
470,470,LOC,Where do hyenas live ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
471,471,HUM,Who is the `` Queen Mother '' ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
472,472,ENTY,What 's the most commonly-spoken language in Belgium ?,lang,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADV', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'GPE', '']"
473,473,HUM,Who has more DNA - a man or a woman ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
474,474,DESC,What are Maid-Rites ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
475,475,ENTY,"What children 's tale contains the line : `` Come , Cinderslut , and hold this skein of wool for me '' ?",cremat,"['PRON', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
476,476,HUM,What level of government or governmental agency is responsible for dealing with racism ?,gr,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
477,477,NUM,How many referees work a soccer game ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
478,478,ENTY,What cocktail do you concoct with whisky and sweet vermouth ?,food,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
479,479,ENTY,How do you say `` fresh '' in Spanish ?,termeq,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'NORP', '']"
480,480,DESC,What do bee hives do in cranberry bogs ?,desc,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
481,481,DESC,What caused the Lynmouth floods ?,reason,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORG', '', '']"
482,482,NUM,When is the Tulip Festival in Michigan ?,date,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', '', 'GPE', '']"
483,483,HUM,"Who came up with the name , El Nino ?",ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'PART', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'ORG', 'ORG', '']"
484,484,ENTY,What movie did Madilyn Kahn star in with Gene Wilder ?,cremat,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
485,485,ENTY,What type of bridge is the Golden Gate Bridge ?,other,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', 'FAC', 'FAC', 'FAC', 'FAC', '']"
486,486,HUM,What dictator has the nickname `` El Maximo '' ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
487,487,HUM,What stereo manufacturer is `` Slightly ahead of its time '' ?,gr,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT', 'ADV', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
489,489,HUM,What TV sitcom character had the maiden name Ethel Potter ?,ind,"['DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', '']"
490,490,ENTY,What was the first Lifesaver flavor ?,food,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'ORDINAL', 'ORG', '', '']"
491,491,HUM,Who kept the most famous diary in the English language ?,ind,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'LANGUAGE', '', '']"
492,492,LOC,Where can I find out the top 1 singles ?,other,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'PART', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', 'CARDINAL', '', '']"
493,493,NUM,How many degrees cooler is the inside of a cucumber than the air outside ?,count,"['ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '']"
494,494,HUM,What Spanish artist painted Crucifixion ?,ind,"['PRON', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', 'NORP', '', '', '', '']"
495,495,ENTY,What is the Jewish bible called ?,cremat,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', 'NORP', '', '', '']"
496,496,DESC,Why is the grass green ?,reason,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '', '']"
497,497,DESC,What is a firewall ?,def,"['PRON', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['', '', '', '', '']"
